I mean, you can ignore it, but that's your side, my friend.
Like I said, you were the one that
tried to derail this argument by bringing that.
It's just because of my argument.
I'm saying immigrants are good to America.
People on your side are saying, we should leave.
Not me, me and you.
And I asked you, what type of immigrants
are we talking about?
Immigrants overall.
Overall.
So you believe that people that come here without any respect
to our laws and our borders are going
to be good for this country.
No, of course not.
So you can't say that all immigrants overall.
I never said all immigrants.
I said immigrants overall.
Immigrants overall doesn't mean all immigrants.
Sorry to break that to you.
All right, so we have to make sure
that the people are coming here have the good intent
of this country in mind.
Agreed?
Yes.
Irrelevant to my claim, but agreed.
But when you have undocumented immigration going on,
you can't vet that.
You can't make sure about that.
Let me, real quick, talk about my background.
There is no American embassy in Iran.
So in order to come here, you have
to stay in line for four years, and you
have to go through some serious vetting procedure to get here.
But I made it.
And that process has to be in place,
because you don't want terrorists to fill this country.
I made it, too.
I'm an American citizen.
I went through lots of vetting.
I took my test.
And that's how it should be.
But the guy over there wants us to leave.
But?
But.
But he wants us to leave.
When people.
So people don't really care about vetting, do they?
It's not really about vetting, is it, my friend?
But people should not have the right.
You're in denial.
People should not have the right to ignore
our borders and our laws.
What about those of you who don't ignore the borders?
Should we get to stay?
Of course.
But he says we shouldn't.
Vaughn.
I'm not debating him.
You kind of are, because you're all together on this.
No, I'm debating you.
OK.
And I'm pointing out to you that your argument is in bad faith,
because these guys are actually speaking the truth,
and you're in denial about who's on your side.
He wants you gone.
I never claim that I'm on their side or they're on my side.
I'm here to debate you.
All right, pause.
You've been voted out by the majority.
Please return to your seat.
Nice to meet you.